It's cute, isn't it?
かわいいですよね
That's not Totoro.
トトロじゃないよ、それ
Miffy?
ミフィー?
Does it say Miffy?
ミフィーって書いてあるの?
I wondered what that meant.
何のことだと思いました
Is that so?
そういうこと?
This is all I know too.
俺もこれしか知らないけど
Have you ever connected like this?
こうやって繋いだことあるでしょ?
there is.
あります
What about kissing?
キスとかは?
I did.
しました
tomorrow.
明日
How far did you go?
どこまでしたの?
I did it before I put it in.
入れる前までしました
入れる前までしたんだ
Did you try to include it?
入れようとはしたの?
I tried to put it in, but it hurt so I fell asleep.
入れようとはしたんですけど、 痛かったから眠りました
It hurt a little.
ちょっと痛かったんだ
nice.
いいね
Because it's cute.
かわいいから
I'll look at it.
眺めちゃうね
Can I take it off?
外していい?
Totoro.
トトロ
Does it say Miffy?
ミフィーって書いてあるの?
What is Miffy?
ミフィーって
I think I should write it.
書 いちゃおうかな
what happened?
どうしたの?
It's Totoro.
トトロでさ
kind.
優しい
gently.
優しく
Was it touched?
触られた?
I was touched.
触られた
I like the style.
スタイルいいね
kind.
優しい
You're so kind.
優しいよね
I thought about it myself.
自分で考えた
Have you ever been woken up?
覚められたことあるでしょ?
Did you wake up?
覚められた?
It's still hidden.
まだ隠れてるよ
Have you ever been pointed at?
指言われたことある?
Couldn't you point it out?
指言えなかったの?
I couldn't say it.
言えなかった
amazing.
すごい
It's beautiful, body.
綺麗だね、体
copper?
どう?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Are you serious?
本気?
You're so kind.
優しいね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
it hurts?
痛 い?
straight.
真っ直ぐ